[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Napoleon Dynamite had a favorite animal that he liked to draw.  What was it?", "correct_answer": "a liger (tiger and lion mix)", "incorrect_answers": ["a dinosaur", "a dragon", "a unicorn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of The Rolling Stones song, mentioned in the book Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas, that couldnt be used in the movie version, because there wasnt enough money to buy its rights?", "correct_answer": "Sympathy for the Devil", "incorrect_answers": ["Angie", "Paint it Black", "Start me up"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This US President granted a posthumous pardon to Robert Edward Lee, a general of the Confederate forces during the American Civil War.", "correct_answer": "Gerald Ford", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard Nixon", "John Kennedy", "Lyndon Johnson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If an atom loses an electron its electromagnetic balance is disturbed and the atom decays releasing  ionizing particles and a large amount of energy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This city state, also called Ragusa, was first to recognize the independence of the newly formed United States of America.", "correct_answer": "Dubrovnik", "incorrect_answers": ["Vatican", "Monaco", "Malta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How tall is a typical zebra at the shoulder?", "correct_answer": "4 feet (1.2 m)", "incorrect_answers": ["6 feet (1.8 m)", "5 1/2 feet (1.6 m)", "3 feet (0.9 m)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All domestic chickens can be traced back to which bird?", "correct_answer": "The Red Jungle Fowl", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wild Turkey", "The Macaw", "The Amazon Rain Forest Chicken"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rakia is a strong alcoholic drink made of various fruits, usually grapes, plums or apricots.", "correct_answer": "Bulgaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Hungary", "Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In March 1981, Vivienne Westwood presented her first runway show in London, introducing which famous collection?", "correct_answer": "The Pirate Collection", "incorrect_answers": ["The Situationists Collection", "The Seditionary Collection", "The Boudoir Collection"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The store in the movie The Goonies is located at what intersection?", "correct_answer": "37th Street and Highway 30", "incorrect_answers": ["27th Street and Leif Erickson Dr.", "48th Street and Highway 40", "29th Street and Highway 30"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do the police describe Jonathan Brewster, a character in Arsenic and Old Lace?", "correct_answer": "Looks like Karloff", "incorrect_answers": ["Pop-eyes, talks with a German accent", "Short and balding.", "Tall with many scars."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played Elizabeth Brooke McGuire in the television show, Lizzie McGuire?", "correct_answer": "Hillary Duff", "incorrect_answers": ["Lalaine Vergara", "Hallie Todd", "Ashlie Brillault"]}]